A hospital in the city of Dnipro has been completely destroyed in a Russian robot attack.
At least two people must have been killed and more than 30 injured -
- In what Ukraine describes as a war crime.
Dnipro is one of the larger cities in eastern Ukraine-
- And its geographical location also shows its importance.
Therefore, Dnipro has also become a kind of logistical hub.
Both militarily, for Ukraine's military, but also for civilian organizations -
- As aid organizations or media.
Many are based on Dnipro in their work on eastern Ukraine.
Fortezza Bachmut!
Pictures from Russian news agency Tass provide a rare insight from inside Bachmut.
Three: They are relatively small and therefore more difficult for air defense to detect.
The drones have become a well -known detail during the Ukraine War -
- And made the light directed against Russia and Iran's relationship.
Western countries point to in -depth military cooperation between Russia and Iran-
- Not at least around these patrol robots.
This is nothing that Iran disputes in substance, but on the other hand describes man - -
–Wester reactions as hysterical or as an attempt -
- Keeping Iranian products away from the Russian market.
Stop for Iranian drones!
After the last attacks, Ukraine has now introduced -
–50 year long sanctions against Iran, including
Total Trade Ban with the Land-
- And a travel ban for Iranians through Ukraine.
Ukraine says this will have consequences and western countries -
- Have tried to push Iran not to send these patrol robots to Russia.
In fact, experts - admit the experts -
- It is very difficult to do something about this, for example with sanctions.
One of the main causes is that there is an open transport route -
- Between Russia and Iran across the Caspian Sea.
Russia's capital Moscow has been attacked with several drones -
- Computer Russian authorities.